[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：Array是基本的数据结构之一。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Array is one of the fundamental data structures.
它是一系列连续的内存跨度，分为相同大小
It's a contiguous series of span of memory divided into equal sized
插槽，其中每个插槽由一个数字索引，非常快，非常有效。
slots where each slot is indexed by a number, very fast, very efficient.
JavaScript没有类似的东西。
JavaScript doesn't have anything like that.
相反，JavaScript所做的是当JavaScript的第一个版本忘记放置
Instead what JavaScript does is while the first version of JavaScript forgot to put
数组，人们很好地理解了这一点，我们可以只使用一个对象，对吧。
arrays in, and people figured out that well, we can just use an object, right.
我们可以使用括号表示法，我们可以传递数字，将数字转换为
We can use the bracket notation, we can pass numbers, the numbers get turned into
字符串和它的工作方式有点像数组，这仍然是我们所做的。
strings and it all kind of works like an array sort of and that's still what we do.
所以现在有一个数组数据类型。
So there is now an array data type.
它从Object继承，索引被转换为字符串和
It inherits from object and the indices are converted into strings and
用于检索和存储值。
used to retrieve and store values.
好消息是，这对于稀疏数组非常有效。
The good news is, that is extremely efficient for sparse arrays.
不幸的是，我们不做稀疏数组的事情，
Unfortunately, we don't do sparse array stuff,
我们几乎只做密集数组的事情，这是非常低效的。
we're almost exclusively doing dense array stuff and it's very inefficient for that.
它提供的另一个优点是不需要提供长度或
One other advantage it provides is that there is no need to provide a length or
创建数组时键入。
type when creating an array.
我们可以只说空尖括号。
We can just say empty angle brackets.
这是一个新的数组，然后你可以添加任何你想要的东西。
That's a new array and then you can add as much stuff as you want to it.
您不必担心越界错误，因为它实际上并不是
You don't have to worry about out of bounds errors because it's not really
一个数组，它是一个哈希表。
an array, it's a hash table.
所以每个值都是平衡的。&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：数组，
So every value is in balance. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Arrays,
与对象不同，具有特殊的长度属性，并且
unlike objects, have a special length property, and
该属性总是比最高整数下标大1，
that property is always one larger than the highest integer subscript,
其不必与阵列中的元素数量相同。
which is not necessarily the same as number of elements in the array.
所以我们可以用Object literal或Array literal创建一个数组。
So we can make an array with an object literal or with an array literal.
使用括号表示法，
Using the bracket notation,
我们可以用逗号分隔多个表达式，
we can have multiple expressions in there separated by commas,
它们中的每一个都将为元素提供一个值。
each of those will provide a value to an element.
我们可以通过为数组的当前长度赋值来追加到数组
We can append to an array by assigning to it's current length
看起来真的很奇怪，但很管用。
which is really weird looking, but it works.
因此在本例中，myList.length为3，所以我们将分配给它，
So in this case, myList.length is 3, so we'll assign to it,
现在长度将变成3加1，
and the length will now be turned into 3 plus 1,
4.&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：数组随附
4. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Arrays come with
一组比对象更有趣的方法。
a more interesting set of methods than objects have.
对象几乎没有来自object.prototype的有用内容。
Objects have very little useful stuff coming from object.prototype.
这些东西都存储在array.prototype中，更有用的集合。
This stuff is all stored in array.prototype, much more useful set.
我们会看看其中的几个。
We'll look at a couple of these.
例如，有一种排序方法，在这里我们可以获取一个数字数组并
For example, there's sort method, where we can take an array of numbers and
我们可以解决的。
we can sort it.
有人看到这里发生了什么吗？&gt；&gt；扬声器2：[听不见]
So anybody see what's going on here? &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [INAUDIBLE]
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：但它正在排序
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: But it's sorting on
弦。
the strings.
所以它获取每个数字，将其转换为字符串，然后获取另一个，
So it takes each number, converts it into a string, takes the other one,
将其转换为字符串，比较它们，并在日志时间内完成此操作。
converts it into a string, compares them and it does that in log times.
太可怕了。
It's awful.
所以幸运的是，排序可以
So fortunately, sort can take
一个函数参数，它接收成对的值和
a function argument which receives pairs of values and
它根据它们的相对大小返回负1、0或1。
it returns minus 1, 0 or 1 based on their relative magnitudes.
所以你可以覆盖这个可怕的行为，但是默认情况下它是愚蠢的。
So you can override this terrible behaviour, but It's stupid by default.
您可以从数组中删除元素，但它不会执行您预期的操作。
You can delete an element from an array, but it doesn't do what you expect.
因此，通常需要使用拼接方法来闭合孔。
So usually, you want to use the splice method to close up a hole.
让我来演示一下。
So let me demonstrate that.
这里我们得到了一个包含四个元素的数组
So here we've got an array containing four elements and
我想删除第一个元素。
I want to delete element number one.
这将在其中留下一个空洞，该空洞被标识为未定义的值。
That'll leave a hole in it which is identified as the undefined value.
如果尝试从数组中检索值，并且
If you try to retrieve a value from an array and
它没有该元素，它返回未定义的值。
it doesn't have that element, it returns the undefined value.
因此，如果你想摆脱这种情况，请使用拼接方法。
So if you want to get rid of that, use a splice method.
你说去元素一，删除一个元素。
You say go to element one, delete one element.
然后，您将得到一个更像您预期的数组。
Then you'll get in an array that's more like what you were expecting.
它这样做的方式是删除第一个元素，检索第二个元素，
The way it does that is it deletes element one, it retrieves element two,
删除元素二，将其作为元素一重新插入。
deletes element two, re inserts it as element one.
它转到第三个元素，读取它，删除它，重新插入它作为第二个元素。
It goes to element three, reads it, deletes it, re inserts it as element two.
不快。&gt；&gt；扬声器3：哇。
It's not fast. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Whoa.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：[笑]
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: [LAUGH]
人群中有一种恐惧的表情。
There's a look of horror in the crowd.
好的，因为对象和数组是由相同的材料组成的
Okay, so because objects and arrays are made out of the same stuff in this
语言，原来你只能使用其中一种
language, it turns out that you can use just one of them
大多数时候，这是一个非常糟糕的主意，因为有时它很重要。
most of the time which is a really bad idea because sometimes it matters.
而且因为它有时很重要，我建议，使用正确的。
And because it sometimes matters, I recommend, use the right one.
当名称为任意字符串时使用对象，
Use objects when the names are arbitrary strings,
当名称为连续整数时使用数组。
use arrays when the names are sequential integers.
不要被术语关联数组所迷惑。
Don't be confused by the term Associative Array.
在JavaScript中，关联数组称为对象。
In JavaScript, the Associative Array is called the object.